[{"answer": "We're not -- we're not at that point yet.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "If they do something, should America do anything, or does America keep out of this?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Look.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Have you seen anything like that?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, I think he will be getting a certain amount of heat from some people because there's no doubt the sanctions are having a big effect.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, it's understandable.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Am I wrong to feel so pessimistic?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, you never know until the election actually happens.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Do you think it could still go either way?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "If you were going to be the incumbent come November the 7th, what kind of thing should the American administration, whoever it is, be looking to do quite quickly to try and stem this economic tide downward, which is going on all over the world?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, I don't -- I --", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "So you would have known?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Would you have known who wrote \"Rule Britannia\"?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Well, the one thing I know is that in whatever country and whatever culture, whatever continent, whatever part of the world Bill Clinton was standing, everyone else better watch out, because he is the total master and he would -- he's just -- the thing that I always say about Bill Clinton is, the fascinating thing about him as a politician is that he's unbelievably smart and smart enough so that he doesn't come across as unbelievably smart.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Would that complete the peace project for you?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Oh, there's no doubt about that, I'm afraid.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Who would win?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "I don't think it's quite as big a problem as you've made it out to be.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "This is -- this is a big problem for Mitt Romney, isn't it?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "My heavens, I take my hat off to her.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Pretty impressive, Kate, isn't she?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "I think she's able to cope with it.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Do you worry about the pressure that you know she's going to be facing?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I'm doing very well, thank you.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Sarah Ferguson, how are you?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "It's been a very British show, actually.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Well, two things, really.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What advice do you give Kate for how to get through it and how to deal with it?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think it's very difficult because you are always -- you always worry so much.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "How do you deal with that generally?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think that's very good.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "How is that?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I think that education is the route out of poverty, because it gives the knowledge of survival.", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What are you trying to achieve with this?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Is there a touch of Sarah Ferguson in \"Ballerina Rosie?\"", "docId": "120927pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "And if you want to go and buy the book, I am not going to tell you the end of the tale, but you does \"Ballerina Rosie\" manage to do her pirouettes?", "qSentId": 543}]